# **Mohammad Rajib Uddin**

8/9 Block C Lalmatia Dhaka 1207 Bangladesh

Email: md.rajibuddin58@gmail.com

Phone:01632201853

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/mdrajibuddin/



#### **Career Profile**

Graduate from one of the leading research schools in Australia. Lecturer on business administration with experience in different aspects of business, starting from Banking, Logistics, supply chain management, market research, marketing management, data analytics and human resource.

#### **Education:**

Master of Business specializing in Marketing University of Wollongong Australia Result: Credit (Weighted Average Mark of 73.79%). Passing year mid 2018

Graduate Certificate in Business University of Wollongong Australia Result: Credit (Weighted Average mark of 73.33%). Passing year mid 2017

Bachelor of Business Administration Independent University of Bangladesh Major: Marketing, Minor: Finance GPA:3.17 Passing year 2015

A level: Mathematics and Economics. Passing year 2010

O level: Economics, Art & Design, English, Bangla, Math B, Accounting. Passing year 2008

School: S.F.X Green Herald INT School

On Going Work for Publication: I am currently working on a paper about transforming businesses with artificial intelligence, big data analytics, deep learning and cloud computing technology with professor Shahriar Akhter from the University of Wollongong Australia. The paper is focused on literature reviews of academic journals, the goal is to provide a detailed analysis on how businesses perform by using the technologies.

Career as a Research Assistant: Name of the Project: Frontline Employees Service Adaptiveness in Bigdata driven Services Environment; Accelerating service productivity using bigdata. I have worked as a research assistant for a year under the supervision of Professor Shahriar Akter, my task was to conduct qualitative interviews with industry leaders of Big-Data analytics and technology. After the interview my second task was to transcribe the interviews.

### **Experience**

May 2019-August 2019

Organization: Independent University

Bangladesh

Position: Adjunct Lecturer Department: Marketing

August 2018-Janunary 2019

Organization: Drake Logistics LTD (Drake logistics offer logistic support to varies

businesses)

Position: Mail room and logistic

Supervisor

November 2018 (One-month contract

under Drake Logistics)

Organization: Credit Suisse Australia Human Resource Project Assistant

January 2018-December 2018

Organization: University of Wollongong

Australia

Position: Research Assistant

October 2017- May 2018

Organization: King's Own Institute

(Australia)

Position: Casual Exam Invigilator

December 2017-February 2018
Organization: Myer Australia
Position: Casual Sales Assistant for

Christmas only

May 2016-November 2016

Organization: Woolworths Australia
Position: Replenishment Team Member

September 2015- November 2015

Organization: Blend PVT LTD (Bangladesh)

Position: Marketing Executive

February 2015-April 2015

Organization: Standard Chartered Bank

Bangladesh
Position: Intern

## Language and professional skills

Fluent in Bangla and English.
Computer skills: Advanced Operational command in SPSS statistic Software, MS Word, Power point and have beginner's operational knowledge in Excel.

### **Additional details**

Date of Birth: 17/June/1990

Sex: Male

Father's Name: Mohammad Reaz Uddin

Ahmed

Occupation: Businessman Mother's name: Zebunessa Occupation: Superwomen

### References

Dr Shahriar Akter

Associate professor Faculty of Business

Discipline: Marketing Sydney Business School

University of Wollongong Australia UOW sakter@uow.edu.au +61 02 4221

3377

Grant Mackenzie
Chief Executive Officer

P: (Australia) +61 2 9273 0601 P: (New Zealand) +64 9 379 5610

m: +61 (0) 404 144 957 e:

grant.mackenzie@swisspost.com